J recognition
wait
lol
If you want to fall in love, shake up,
shake up, shake up
The goal is to lose weight, lose 3.5kg
Lose weight, lose weight, lose weight
Don't be afraid of the future
I hope everyone will work hard
Then, please take a look at the
situation
OK!
Situation
What?
Part-time staffs are in love with you?
It's difficult
I'm in
Tsubosuke Kalbi
It's the one in the pot
Co-star
Tsuji's Tanami
I'll draw another person
Yoshikawa Hiyori
The last scene
I'll hit her head
The staffs are going to see it
The last scene
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready
Ready, start!
I'm looking forward to it
It's been a while since I ate meat
I'm so happy
It's coming soon
Sorry to keep you waiting
It's here
Great
This is Tsubosuke Kalbi
Thank you
I'll eat it
I'm sorry. I'll be right there.
It's a rare smell.
I think that person is scary.
I'm scared of people.
I'm going to eat this.
I'll eat the meat first.
Is it okay to eat the meat that's in
the bag?
I'm going to eat it.
I'll show you.
Wow!
I'll eat it.
Really?
Wow!
Did she bring this?
She is doing her best.
I wonder when she will come to the next
hospital.
Excuse me, did you forget to bring a
water?
I brought it for the first time since I
started working.
It was a little heavy, but it was
delicious, so please grill it well and
eat it.
I'll grill it.
A little...
Do you want me to grill it?
Oh, is that okay?
I'll grill it.
Thank you very much.
If you don't grill it properly, you'll
break your stomach.
Please grill it properly.
I think it's good to grill it.
It's cool.
No, it's not.
It's been a while since I started
working.
Is that so?
How old are you?
I'm 18 years old.
18 years old?
I'm one year younger than you.
What kind of person do you like?
I like a person who is lazy.
I haven't had a girlfriend yet.
Why? Do you want to show off?
I'd like you to grill it.
Oh, that's good.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay if I grill it?
Yes.
It's big, so...
It's good.
It looks delicious.
It's good, isn't it?
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
Please subscribe to our channel.
It's better to wear a hat.
Is the school nearby?
Yes, it's close to here.
I go to the school called ANLA.
I see.
I go to ANLA.
It's close.
It's a neighborhood.
Pio is about to be called.
I'm busy.
I see.
I have to go.
Please hurry.
You are so busy.
Please wait a moment.
You are going to do it.
I'm curious.
I think it's good.
Can you do it?
Hiyorin, go over there.
Are you OK?
I'm sorry.
I'm OK.
You are called.
Please wait a moment.
Do your best.
Thank you.
Go!
I have to go.
The meat is burning.
How was the meat?
I haven't eaten it yet.
You are cute.
Please give me a bite.
It was very long.
It's soft.
It's delicious.
The meat is thick.
Thank you, Mr. Sugogawa.
I'll visit your restaurant.
I'll visit your restaurant anytime.
Finally!
We're here, at their first restaurant
or store, And we're eating grilled meat
for the first time!
Perfect timing!
I'll go with the item.
It's ice cream!
It's a Bambi.
The other one is...
It's a Caname.
The last one is...
It's a laughing doll.
Caname's role?
Caname is a friend.
She's a friend who's here for the first
time.
Fujimoto is a friend who's interested
in Julia.
She's going to make ice cream for her.
She's going to make it for her.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Ready, action!
What are you going to do?
Fujimoto is going to make it.
It's cute.
I'll put it in the first.
I'll put cereal.
I'll put cocoa.
I like it.
I heard you like mushroom.
I'll put caramel.
I'll put ice cream.
What are you doing?
I'll eat with Kanami.
Look at this.
This corner.
I'll put ice cream.
I'll put various things.
It's great.
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to her.
She is over there.
Do you often do this?
I'll put anything I want.
This is my first time.
I'll put tomato.
I'll put 10.
I'll put 30.
I'll put 40.
It's big.
It's not big.
I'll put apple.
I like lemon.
Do you like it?
I like it.
She will be happy.
I'll put it in the middle.
I'll put colorful star.
It's good.
Do you like mushroom?
I said I like it.
I want to do it, too.
I did it.
What are you doing?
What are you making?
Ice cream?
It's cute.
Wait a minute.
What?
Look.
I made ice cream.
Who made it?
I like ice cream.
I think about it all the time.
I eat ice cream anytime.
Do you know?
I think I like it.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's sparkling.
It's cute.
It's sparkling all the time.
I really like it.
Do you?
Yes.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
It's not ice cream.
Don't put it in your mouth.
I got it.
I like it.
It's okay.
Ice cream is safe.
Look.
I made it for you.
Thank you.
Take it.
My favorite mushroom and lemon are on
it.
It's cute.
Thank you.
It was cute.
Please subscribe to this channel.
woo-ooh
Is it okay?
It's so good.
Julia's love is solidified.
Hiyori, please draw a card.
I'll draw.
It's the day before the important test.
The day before the important test.
Buns.
Buns is a bread.
The cheering song is this.
Koizumi-kun.
Ohade-san.
The last one.
While being angry.
That's not right.
Are you ready?
I'm looking forward to it.
Good luck.
Ready, start!
I'm sorry for the day before the test.
I'm serious.
I'm smart, so it's okay.
But suddenly...
I'm stupid.
Shut up.
Oh, it's gone.
I'll do it.
Okay.
I can do it if I'm in the top 50.
Really?
Pio chose buns this time.
I chose the ingredients I like and made
original buns.
I chose hamburger.
I chose the menu that I can make.
It looks fun.
I chose the one I like.
I chose meat.
Do you like meat?
You like buns, don't you?
I can change my mind.
I think I can do well on the test
tomorrow.
I'm going to make a bun.
Isn't it too strict for me?
If it's not strict, how long should I
make a bun?
I don't know.
Are you OK?
Oh, no.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Dear Enlac,
I'm sorry for burning your delicious
buns while you were away.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
I'm going to get myself together.
I've done my homework the day before
the test.
I'm going to make you an original
burger.
A burger?
Yes, an original burger.
First, I'm going to check your health.
It's fun to make a burger.
Do you like cheese?
Yes, I like cheese.
The last social test was 9 points.
I thought it would be dangerous if
Koizumi didn't teach me.
I'm going to teach you.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
Really?
Yes.
I'm stupid but I can do it.
I can do it.
I can do it more than I do.
Isn't it great?
You are doing great.
I can do it.
Hey, I'm going to be angry.
Sorry.
If you get too excited, I'll make you
angry.
Sorry.
What should I do?
I'll do my best.
Do you want tomatoes?
She is a little angry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm a little angry.
I'm sorry.
I'm angry.
You are cute.
Thank you.
Koizumi-kun, I love you!
Cut!
That was great!
Where are you putting it?
It looks so good!
I want you to try it.
Do you want to try it?
Do you want to try the orange burger?
I'll try it.
It looks so good.
Here it comes!
You ate a lot of it.
The meat is juicy and delicious.
The cheese is stretchy.
I'm happy.
We finished filming the drama!
We'll be doing the judging.
We have Matsumura from Yakiniku
Restaurant Anrakutei and Yokozawa from
Enraku.
Please come in!
Please give us your evaluation of the
drama.
This time, we'll be judging based on
the fun of the date.
Is it okay?
Enraku is not just a restaurant.
We want you to feel the fun of the
restaurant.
We hope you'll enjoy the situation.
That's why we're judging based on that.
We have the results.
We have a special prize for you.
The prize is 3,000 yen for the
Anrakutei food test.
We'll announce the 3rd place!
The 3rd place is...
Oharu!
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
I've been playing with Haru for a
while.
I enjoyed the feeling of stretching.
Thank you!
I felt a lot of tension.
I'll give you a present from the
manager.
Thank you!
Next, I'll announce the second place.
The second place is 5,000 yen.
I'm so happy!
The smell is amazing!
I'll announce the second place.
The second place is Julia.
It was fun.
It was fun, but the topping was so
good.
It was so good.
Thank you.
The first place is...
It's 10,000 yen for the Sanraku High
School Exams.
I'll announce the second place.
The first place is Hiyorin.
Really?
I was told to eat a bun, but it was so
fun that I ate it.
The cheese was so good.
It was so good that I ate it with
cheese.
Thank you.
Is it okay?
The second place is...
It's 10,000 yen for the Sanraku High
School Exams.
It was so good.
There are so many tables.
I'm looking forward to eating.
You are eating ice cream.
This is the second one.
I'll eat it.
I put salt in it by mistake.
Do you like meat?
I'm eating it.
It's delicious.
I'll eat it.
It looks really delicious.
I'm eating it.
It's so soft.
It's hot.
Please come to eat Yakiniku Tabehondai
Enryaku-san.
It's delicious.
Let's eat.
It looks so delicious.
Please subscribe to this channel.
If you fall in love, shake up, shake
up, shake a lick and shake up.
We aim to become a mighty を
I want to perform live with my flexible
body.
I will definitely show you a more
powerful appearance than last year.
I'm really looking forward to the
performance of Senzenburi, who will
support me.
Our mystery story has just begun.
I think that everyone can see it,
everyone can see it, and the
possibilities are limitless.
If I'm with Senzenburi and the members,
I'm sure I can make a big wall into a
small wall.
We believe in that.
So, please wait for me, Nakano Sakura!
I'll be your...
Dash! Dash! Let's chase our dreams!
Dash! Dash! Dash! Never waking up from
this dream!
If I'm with you, I can make my dreams
come true!
I'll be your... Dash! Dash! Dash! Never
waking up from this dream!
Urgent need of JP–EN translators! Apply
in Discord! Join our Discord for all AI-
chan news! https://discord.gg-
writen.time.as